I love having technology strapped to my
face shot I
school my house
yeah cloth what the hell list what the
hell is this
the these our Google Glasses the newest
piece of technology that will change the
way
everyone lives whenever I start wearing
his ugly classes
I am answers call
they did you meet the park at 10 I wanna
show you something
sure see their I cool but do
are you taking a dump work no
I could see you are on video chat of
paul got
%uh see you at 10 Google Glasses
optimizes your life by showing you add
specifically tailored to your online
shopping history
however because Galway what's really
going you
it's not well haha you can purchase a
band-aid for your welcome
and the best the upper band aid on D-day
would you like to purchase don't have
time for that
I'm bleeding now and hard showing all
results for band aid within a 5-mile
radius
I'll come on well I Luna
for Google Glasses integrates Google
Maps with full navigation
turn left turn right
keep looking forward keep looking
forward
keep walking forward a man you almost
here
I have no idea on did what happened here
I ran into a couple balls
okay yeah anyway you pick me up some
chicken nuggets
ok and take a picture that mural a
Jefferson Street sure am
taking photos has never been easier
take a picture and send it to end the
hell
if mind sending pictured here any
Dr no of what Duff
Google Glasses are also helpful in
teaching you how to cook
or showing you the ingredients in your
food when chicken nugget for these homes
are you off
home paul hasn't
this chicken nugget contains chicken
breast breadcrumbs
black plastic sawdust a crackdown West
percent to
whale c'mon fecal matter
so as you can see Google glasses will
change the way you live your life
hey man well hey you're late sciences
these stupid classes so what you want
0 haha I just wanted some chicken
nuggets you take a bite out of this
that is good for you II gotta run
by of
from me the nearest direction to a
plastic surgeon upon fix my broken ass
nose
and Google glasses feature an impressive
want
hour battery life what's up look to
well you backhoe Google Glasses
are you ready for the future
just see bloopers and deleted scenes and
this click the video
right here so I am just gravitated your
crotch
thanks for subscribing now subscribe on
YouTube videos a factor last working
I'll do I don't want that all got it